Brigitte, you're one of my best agents.
So, I'll give you one chance to explain
why you put a cat in a jetpack. I know
it seems crazy, but she can help, can't
you, Fika?
Oh, good girl.
>> [sighs]
>> I should have stayed retired.
Now, if I give you this treat, you'd
better not tell your ma, you hear?
Cassidy, you're going to teach her to
beg.
Aw, but she has been so good lately,
hasn't she?
A cat in A JETPACK?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE CATTING ME.
>> [laughter]
>> REINHARDT, I DO BELIEVE IT'S kitten me.
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS. SHE'S NOT A BABY.
Zebedeh la hayed WILL BE PERILOUS.
SHARPEN THOSE CLAWS, FIKA.
Or perhaps our enemy will change their
ways when they see HOW CUTE YOU ARE.
I think my allergies are acting up.
Oh.
>> [snorts]
>> No wonder.
Fika, were you playing on my desk again?
You accidentally tripped my security
systems.
Aw, it's okay. I'll find you something
else to play with.
You remind me of an old friend from the
lunar colony.
You're both smart and cute and love
finding trouble. I hope I can introduce
you to him one day.
How delightful to see human arrogance
contradicted by a cat, no less.
You'd better stay out of trouble out
there. Understand, recruit?
And I'll know if you've been sneaking
treats between missions.
You're so cute, I could just squish you
to bits.
Nah, don't worry. I'm just pulling your
tail.
Ah, if only you were a black cat. You
could help me ward off evil.
Sorry, jeez. You're fine the way you
are, okay?
So, I'm trying to ask everybody this.
What is your favorite animal?
Uh, yeah. I can see it.
Intelligent, adaptable.
You have the makings of a perfect test
subject.
Though a little dose of obedience would
be appreciated.
Are you speaking to me?
Hm, perhaps I should prioritize cat on
my list of languages to learn.
Aw, hey little guy. Come here.
>> [snorts]
>> Oh, uh,
sorry.
How about you fly me up and I'll make it
rain fire?
Don't make me get the spray bottle,
young lady.
Bad girl, Fica.
Sorry. I mean
Poor bless, Misikat.
Cats don't belong in the sky.
>> [gasps]
>> What about your nine lives?
Only ask me.
That's for chasing Murphy.
For the last time, NO BEGGING.
>> [screaming]
>> MEOWCH.
I HOPE YOU WILL LAND ON your feet.
If you aim to kill me, at least bare
your fangs.
Close your eyes.